Complete!?
The next day
It's the final!
It's the last! Let's have fun!
Kanami!
Hitoka!
Haruka!
Yui!
Tokimeki Tenrenbu!
Rock'n'Roll!
Thank you!
Let's go!
Be careful of the earphones!
We'll put them on the floor.
We'll be back soon.
Bye!
See you later!
Let's go!
Hit it hard!
A little more!
See you later!
Thank you!
The first half of the game is over.
The second half will start again.
The first half is over.
The second half of the game is over.
The third half of the game is over.
Thank you for watching.
마지막으로冠を握る細井愛理子さん
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
I wonder what you think
Now, the party is about to begin!
Hello, producers.
This is Iluminazi.
Thank you for watching today's video.
If you like this video, please
subscribe to our channel.
No! No! No!
started a weird existence
This is a thirty millioniovtain contest
These are the victims Gefühl
I'm a little bit crazy
I'm your JET
Yes, so that you age!
I'll steal your heart, I'll steal your
heart
The end of dance dance
ase
Thank you!
The exciting summer Bicchori Festival
2019, Koshinagara, Tatsunoko, and
Akihiko!
The exciting summer Bicchori Festival
2019, Koshinagara, Tatsunoko, and
I didn't expect to see you in this way.
Hey, Pabrin!
Can you speak?
Try to speak.
Say something.
Pabrin, konnichiwa.
Konnichiwa.
Welcome to the Pinyori Festival!
Let's read a little more.
You're good at dancing.
December 21st is the day of the
Okikuri!
I've heard this voice somewhere before.
Really?
Yes!
I think it's because of yesterday.
Really?
Let's ask more questions.
What do you want to ask?
What is your favorite food?
Welcome to the Pindori Festival!
I'm eating Pindori!
Which one is a boy or a girl?
December 29th.
This is a secret.
But it's not a secret.
I'm eating Pindori!
It's definitely going to be included!
I'm going to make my wish come true!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much!
Yay!
I'll do my best next time.
Me too.
Oh my god!
It ended in a second.
Thank you everyone!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for being the best!
I'm so...
I can't stop crying.
10 minutes!
10 minutes, everyone!
Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for being the best!
Thank you!
Really!
You're so cute!
Really! I love you!
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you, Paburi.
You're a Hakoshu.
Thank you.
Kotoko brought us a lot of gifts.
When I try to hug Paburi,
I can't.
I was trying to hug her face.
You were cute.
Are you okay?
I saw you were worried.
This is cute.
You are so good.
You are so cute.
I'm shy.
Cute.
You are so good.
Thank you.
Let's take a picture with Pabuko.
What do you like?
Kinami.
Everyone, please.
Please show your face.
Let's go.
Thank you for the Bicchuri Festival.
Thank you.
Yeah.
The water was so much.
It was so much.
The water gun was amazing.
We couldn't see it before.
It was like a puddle.
Yeah.
The floor.
I got wet walking.
It was so exciting.
Everyone was so nice.
It was the best.
We became good friends.
Thank you.
We have a lot of things to do.
We will release the second single on
9th of June.
It was the first time to perform.
It's a fun song.
Please check it out.
The release event will be held in
September and October.
Please come and enjoy.
And this fall,
November,
we will hold a Halloween live.
One month tour.
We will hold it.
Please come and enjoy.
Please check our fan page.
There is a video of running.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's the first time to go to the place.
Kyoto, Shizuoka, Ibaraki.
It's the first time to go to Ibaraki.
Please come to see us.
Thank you.
The spicy tour will take place in the
2020 spring!
I'm so happy.
I've been waiting for this.
I was so happy to see you on the ZEPP
tour.
ZEPP tour.
It's a great opportunity.
It's cool.
I forgot to say that I'm going to do a
ZEPP tour.
I'm going to do a ZEPP tour.
I'm going to do a special ZEPP tour.
Everyone, please come and visit us.
We'll be waiting for you.
Everyone, let's follow Toki-chan from
now on.
See you.
Also, Natsuu, you've been sigh.
We've decided on the theme of the
summer!
Please look forward to it!
And the chestnut candy!
We've decided on the schedule for next
summer.
We've already written it down.
You've already written it down?
Yes.
Everyone's already written it down.
We've already written it down.
Please keep up with us!
Please!
See you later!
See you next time!
I want to perform live with my body and
soul.
I will definitely show you a more
powerful performance than last year.
I'm so glad that the fans who support
us are really good.
Our victory story has just begun.
I want to see it with everyone.
I think there is no such thing as a
dream and the possibilities are
limitless.
If we are with the members of Sendai
Music, we can definitely make a big wall
into a small wall.
We believe in that.
So, please wait for us.
Thank you.
Let's Dance! Dance! Dance! Let's follow
our dreams
Dance! Dance! Dance! Dreams that never
wake
We can make it come true if we're
together
I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'll
try.
I'll try to do my best.
Ready, action!
I'm a water fairy.
Me too!
And you?
I'm a cloud fairy.
A cloud fairy?
Where did you come from?
I'm from the world above you all.
That's totally a coincidence.
It's just the beginning.
I'm a rain fairy.
Rain, no.
Please do something about the rain.
It's been raining a lot lately.
I'm starting to get hungry.
It's the sun.
I heard a water drop.
Rain, I was actually lying to everyone.
I'm actually a sun fairy.
It's hot.
So I'll light up everyone.
Bye-bye.
The clouds are flying over the clouds.
I'm going to send you a letter.
What's that?
Ice?
I don't know.
I need happiness.
Cut!
It's not good for everyone.
I think it's because of the power of
the studio.
Let's go to the next one.
What's this?
And it's spinning all the time.
Players can also experience the power
of Google Assistant!
I hate it the most.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of everything.
Translated by Releska